OYEWOLE ABRAHAM IBUKUNOLUWA

Address: Pure Water Junction, Iyana Bodija, Ibadan. +2348163956905 | highbeekay69@gmail.com

SUMMARY

Research-oriented graduate of Anthropology with extensive knowledge in performing research, gathering data, examining groups and cultures, and conducting surveys. Demonstrated knowledge in social media management, information gathering and filming and editing of videos. Proven ability to multitask, learn quickly, and a strong dedication to accuracy. Reliable team member who demonstrate effective communication, interpersonal, and organizational skills.

PROFESSIONAL EXPERIENCE

I-Solution Courier Company- Social Media Manager (Remote)

May 2020 - Present

- Analyse and report social media presence, engagement, and effectiveness on all platforms.
- Serve as a thought leader among others on digital trends and emerging social media technologies.
- Post, and manage updates and responses for all online content on social media.

First Baptist Church, Oke Elerin, Ogbomosho - Social Media Manager/Videographer

2017 - Present

- Analyse and report social media presence, engagement, and effectiveness on all platforms.
- Serve as a thought leader on digital trends and emerging social media technologies.
- Create, post, and manage updates and responses for all online content on social media.
- Supervise crews for installing, operating, and striking audiovisual equipment.
- Control setup, breakdown, and full operation of all audiovisual and lighting gear for events.
- Consistently deliver the highest level of service, accuracy in services.

Rejoice Academy School, Kwasere Village, Kaduna – Teacher(NYSC)

July 2018 - July 2019

- Taught students core subjects, such as Civic Education and Social Studies.
- Rendered academics advice to students for better performance.
- Developed creative ways to get the students involved and engaged in their studies.
- Assessed, recorded, and communicated student performance and progress.
- Contributed to the development of schemes of learning and subject.
- Assessed the development of students and modify teaching style to accommodate different learning needs.

LEADERSHIP EXPERIENCE

Member, Faculty of Art Legislative Council, University of Ibadan.
 In the different legislative sittings throughout an academic year, gained experience how to present reasonable and logical argument, critical thinking and problem solving.

EDUCATION

•	Bachelor's Degree in Anthropology (Second Class Upper) - University of Ibadan, Oyo State	2017
---	--	------

PROFESIONAL CERTIFICATION

•	Google Digital Skills for Africa Program, Google Inc	2019
•	Diploma in Customer Service, Alison.com	2020
•	Johnson Soft Skills Program	2020

AWARDS

Best Graduating Student - Department of Archaeology and Anthropology, University of Ibadan.

2016/2017

SKILLS & EXPERTISE

- Social Media Management.
- Video Editing Skills.
- Data and Information Gathering.
- Time Management.
- Critical Thinking.
- Research and Documentation.

- Judgement and Decision Making.
- Adaptability and Flexibility.
- Emotional Intelligence.
- Proficient in Microsoft Office Suite
- Interpersonal and Communication Skills.
- Commitment & Aspiration